Doctor summary (to see all details, run flutter doctor -v):
[ΓêÜ] Flutter (Channel stable, 3.38.9, on Microsoft Windows [Version 10.0.26100.7623], locale en-IN)
[ΓêÜ] Windows Version (11 Home Single Language 64-bit, 24H2, 2009)
[!] Android toolchain - develop for Android devices (Android SDK version 35.0.0)
    X Flutter requires Android SDK 36 and the Android BuildTools 28.0.3
      To update the Android SDK visit https://flutter.dev/to/windows-android-setup for detailed instructions.
[ΓêÜ] Chrome - develop for the web
[!] Visual Studio - develop Windows apps (Visual Studio Community 2022 17.11.2)
    X Visual Studio is missing necessary components. Please re-run the Visual Studio installer for the "Desktop development with C++" workload, and include these components:
        MSVC v142 - VS 2019 C++ x64/x86 build tools
         - If there are multiple build tool versions available, install the latest
        C++ CMake tools for Windows
        Windows 10 SDK
[ΓêÜ] Connected device (3 available)
[ΓêÜ] Network resources

! Doctor found issues in 2 categories.
